Question: "Facilities and services provided by the OS that assist the programmer in creating programs are in the form of what programs that are not actually part of the OS but are accessible through the OS", Answer: utility Time: 2.0159s ############################# Question: "what is when the processor spends most of its time swapping pages rather than executing instructions", Answer: thrashing Time: 2.0635s ############################# Question: "A what is a collection of memory regions", a. APX b. nucleus c. domain d. page table Peripheral.
Answer: direc- tory Time: 1.7736s ############################# Question: "what is an I/O operation", Answer: supervisor level Time: 1.9975s ############################# Question: "A/An what is a hardware-generated signal to the processor", Answer: An interrupt Time: 2.0100s ############################# Question: "The OS maintains a what_ for each process that shows the frame location for each page of the process", Answer: resident Time: 1.7859s ############################# Question: "A what is an actual location in main memory", Answer: A physical address Time: 1.9934s ############################# Question: "A what is a special type of programming language used to provide instructions to the monitor", Answer: job control language Time: 1.7702s ############################# Question: "The what gives a program access to the hardware resources and services available in a system through the user instruction set architecture supplemented with high-level language library calls", Answer: • Application programming interface Time: 1.9937s ############################# Question: "In Address Spaces of Pentium Memory Management, this memory is viewed as a paged linear address space", Answer: • Unsegmented paged memory Time: 1.8096s ############################# Question: "The what is a program that controls the execution of application programs and acts as an interface between applications and the computer hardware", Answer: 8.1 OPERATING SYSTEM OVERVIEW Operating System Objectives and Functions An OS Time: 2.0878s ############################# Question: "Data that has been organized and logically related to allow access, retrieval, and use of that data is called a", Answer: paging Time: 1.7908s ############################# Question: "Techniques that automatically move program and data blocks into the physical main memory when they are required for execution are called what", Answer: resident monitor Time: 1.9906s ############################# Question: "How many bits of segment reference and offset contained in each virtual address?", Answer: eight Time: 1.7925s ############################# Question: "The what defines the repertoire of machine language instructions that a computer can follow", Answer: The ISA Time: 1.9932s ############################# Question: "A what system works only one program at a time", Answer: uniprogramming Time: 1.7898s ############################# Question: "The what scheduler determines which programs are admitted to the system for processing" Answer: Long-Term Time: 2.0141s ############################# 
